Community Cookbook Collection: Local Organization Non-Profit Cookbooks and Nationally-Published Popular Cookbooks, 1907-2008 TX614.C66
Lilly Library
Community Cookbook Collection: Local Organization Non-Profit Cookbooks and Nationally-Published Popular Cookbooks
1907-2008
2011
Lilly Library
TX614.C66
238 items (13 boxes)
A collection of cookbooks printed in the United States between 1907 and 2008, with particular focus on cookbooks from Indiana.
Access Restrictions
This collection is open for research.
Many collections are housed offsite; retrieval requires advance notice. Please make an appointment a minimum of one week in advance of your visit.
Biographical Note
June Newkirk-Lowe McGlasson, 1921-2011, was an Indiana public school teacher. An accomplished cook, she collected cookbooks and spent much of her time cooking for homeless individuals at the First United Methodist Church in Bloomington, IN.
Arrangement
The collection is organized into two parts; the first consists of community and local cookbooks arranged alphabetically by state and then by organization name, and the second consists of national cookbooks arranged alphabetically by title.
Scope and Content Note
Includes cookbooks printed in the United States between 1907 and 2008, with particular focus on cookbooks from Indiana. Includes cookbooks created for fundraising purposes by local service organizations such as The Junior League, religious and church organizations, and sororities and fraternities. Also includes regionally- and nationally-themed cookbooks focusing on American cuisine and cooking.
Acquisition Information
Gift: 2011
Community Cookbook Collection
- ALABAMA
  - 1. Junior League of Mobile (Box Box 1)
    - Cover Title: Recipe Jubilee!: The Junior League of Mobile, Inc. Spine Title: Recipe Jubilee! Title: Recipe Jubilee published by the Junior League of Mobile, Inc. Description: Mobile, Alabama, 1964. Kingsport: Kingsport Press, Inc. 344 p.: ill.; 24 cm. Includes index. Bound in illustrated boards. (Box Box 1)
  - 2. The Kate Duncan Smith DAR School (Box Box 1)
    - Title: What's Cookin' on Gunter's Mountain. Cover Title: Dedication Day Recipes. Description: Grant, Alabama. 153 p.: ill.; 22 cm. Blue comb binding, with illustrated front cover. (Box Box 1)
- ARIZONA
  - 3. All Saints' Episcopal Church and Day School (Box Box 1)
    - Title: Desert Pot Luck. Spine Title: Desert Pot Luck. Description: Phoenix, Arizona. 246 p.: ill.; 23 cm. Includes index. Plastic ring binding in an illustrated paper binder. (Box Box 1)
  - 4. Phoenix Home Economists in Homemaking (Box Box 1)
    - Cover Title: Favorite Recipes of Arizona Home Economists. Title: A Book of Favorite Recipes. Description: Phoenix, Arizona, 1987. Compiled by Phoenix Home Economists in Homemaking. 124 p.: ill., index; 24 cm. Black comb binding, with illustrated front cover. (Box Box 1)
  - 5. Scottsdale Memorial Hospital Auxiliary (Box Box 1)
    - Cover Title: Prescriptions for Practical Dining: A collection of Favorite Recipe from the members of Scottsdale Memorial Hospital Auxiliary, Scottsdale Arizona, 1984. Title: Prescription for Practical Dining compiled by Scottsdale Memorial Hospital Auxiliary. Description: Scottsdale, Arizona, 1984. 120 p.: ill., index; 23 cm. Red comb binding, with illustrated front cover. (Box Box 1)
  - 6. Tuscan Symphony Women's Association (Box Box 1)
    - Cover Title: But can you eat the desert? Title: The Tucson Symphony Women's Association proudly presents its first cook book to further support and promote the growth and development of the Tucson Symphony Orchestra. Description: Tucson, AZ, 1973. "Printed in the U.S.A. by North American Press of Kansas City"-Back cover. 364 p.: ill.; 23 cm. Brown comb binding, with index and section tabs. (Box Box 1)
- ARKANSAS
  - 7. The Grandpa Jones Family Dinner Theatre (Box Box 1)
    - Cover Title: Ramona Jones Recipes: The Grandpa Jones Family Dinner Theatre. Description: Mountain View, Arkansas, 1986. By Ramona Jones. 117 p.: ill.; 22 cm. White comb binding, with illustrated front cover. (Box Box 1)
- COLORADO
  - 8. Junior League of Denver, Inc. (Box Box 1)
    - Cover Title: Crème de Colorado Cookbook. Spine Title: Crème de Colorado Cookbook: The Junior League of Denver, Incorporated. Title: Crème de Colorado Cookbook Crème de Colorado...Offering you more than recipes, Offering you Colorado! Description: Denver, Colorado, 1987. 381 p.: ill., index; 28 cm. Bound in illustrated boards. (Box Box 1)
- DELAWARE
  - 9. The Henry Francis du Pont Winterthur Museum (Box Box 1)
    - Cover Title: Winterthur's Culinary Collection. Spine Title: Winterthur's Culinary Collection. Title: Winterthur's Culinary Collection: A Sampler of Fine American Cooking. Description: Winterthur, Delaware, 1983. 198 p.: ill., index; 25 cm. White comb binding, with illustrated front cover. (Box Box 1)
- GEORGIA
  - 10. Mildred Evans Warren (Box Box 1)
    - Cover Title: The Cook's Nook: Southern Cooking. Spine Title: The Cooks Nook. Title: The Cook's Nook Compiled and Illustrated by Mildred Evans Warren. Description: Perry, Georgia, 1967. "Printed by Southern Press, Inc., Macon, Ga."-from title page verso. 343 p.: ill.; 22 cm. White comb binding, with illustrated front cover. (Box Box 1)
  - 11. United Church of Broomfield (Box Box 1)
    - Cover Title: The Gathering: an Ecumenical Collection of Recipes. Spine Title: The Gathering: Sponsored by Women's Fellowship. Title: The Gathering, sponsored by Women's Fellowship. Description: Broomfield, Colorado, 1982. 319 p.: ill., index; 23 cm. Bound in a blue binder with metal rings. (Box Box 1)
- ILLINOIS
  - 12. Jane Shoemaker (Box Box 1)
    - Cover Title: Pine Creek Re-Collection of out home recipes. Cover: Pine Creek Re-Collection of Outhome Recipes. Description: Oregon, Illinois, 1978. By Jane shoemaker, with illustrations by Maja Shoemanker. Inscribed, "Feb. 1979, To Dolly from Forreston American Legion Auxiliary. 112 p.: ill., index; 22 cm. Black comb binding, with illustrated front cover. (Box Box 1)
- INDIANA
  - 13. American Association of University Women (Box Box 1)
    - Cover Title: A. A. U. W. Cook Book. Description: La Porte, Indiana. "Presented by the Fellowship Committee, American Association of University Women." ~110 p.: ill.; 24 cm. Black comb binding, with illustrated front cover. (Box Box 1)
  - 14. American Cancer Society (Box Box 1)
    - Cover Title: Hoosier Hospitality Cookbooks: Crossroads Cookin.' Spine Title: Crossroads Cookin': Hoosier Hospitality. Title: Crossroads Cookin': "Hoosier Hospitality Cookbooks" for the benefit of American Cancer Society, Indiana Division, Inc. Description: Indiana, 1984. 176 p.: graphic ill., index; 23 cm. Black comb binding, with illustrated covers. (Box Box 1)
  - 15. American Cancer Society, Indiana Division (Box Box 1)
    - Cover Title: A Taste of Indiana: Our Hoosier Heritage. Spine Title: A Taste of Indiana: Our Hoosier Heritage. Title: A Taste of Indiana: Our Hoosier Heritage. Description: Indianapolis, Indiana, 1982. American Cancer Society, Indiana Division. 186 p.: ill., index; 23 cm. Yellow comb binding, with illustrated covers. (Box Box 1)
  - 16. American Red Cross (Box Box 1)
    - Cover Title:The Little Red Cookbook. Spine Title:The Little Red Cookbook. Title: The Little Red Cookbook. Published by the American Red Cross. Description: Fort Wayne, Indiana. 190 p.: ill., index; 23 cm. Red comb binding, with illustrated covers. (Box Box 1)
  - 17. Arthur G. B. Aid Society (Box Box 1)
    - Cover Title: Cook Book. Description: Winslow, Indiana, 1949. Compiled by the Arthur G. B. Aid Society. Most of the comb binding is damaged and missing. 68 p.: ill.; 21 cm. (Delicate) Red comb binding, with illustrated front cover. (Box Box 1)
  - 18. Beta Sigma Phi, Delta Sigma Chapter (Box Box 1)
    - Cover Title: The Art of Cooking in Bloomington. Description: Bloomington, Indiana. By Beta Sigma Phi, Delta Sigma Chapter. 45 p.; 24 cm. Brown comb binding, with illustrated covers. (Box Box 1)
  - 19. Beth Bowen (Cookbook) (Box Box 1)
    - Cover Title: Beth Bowen's Favorites. Spine Title: Beth Bowen's Favorites. Title: Beth Bowen's Favorites: Dining with Indiana's First Family. Description: Indianapolis, Indiana, 1978. By Elizabeth (Beth) A. Bowen. Indiana Republican State Committee. 281 p.: ill., index; 23 cm. Plastic ring binding, with illustrated plastic binder and section tabs. (Box Box 1)
  - 20. Beth Bowen (Recipe Cards) (Box Box 1)
    - Cover: Beth Bowen's Favorite Recipes. Description: 27 recipe cards, with illustrations and recipe corrections. In a paper envelope. (Box Box 1)
  - 1. Billie Pat Ritter (Former State Fair Baking Champion) (Box Box 2)
    - Cover Title: Cook Book: Favorite Recipes from Our Best Cooks. Title: A book of favorite recipes compiled by Billie Pat Ritter (Former State Fair Baking Champion). Description: Bloomfield, Indiana, 1978. Kansas City: Circulation Service. 96 p.: ill., index; 23 cm. Black comb binding, with illustrated covers. (Box Box 2)
  - 2. Broad View Pentecostal Church (Box Box 2)
    - Cover Title: Favorite Recipes compiled by the Broad View Ladies Auxiliary, Broad View Pentecostal Church. Description: Bloomington, Indiana, 1977. 118 p.: ill., index; 23 cm. Black comb binding, with illustrated front cover. (Box Box 2)
  - 3. Cheer Guild, Indiana University Hospitals (Box Box 2)
    - Cover Title: The Secret Ingredient: A Collection of Recipes from IU Hospitals Staff and Friends. Description: Indianapolis, Indiana, 1990. Benefits go to the James Whitcomb Riley Children's Hospital. 111 p.: index; 22 cm. In illustrated wrappers. (Box Box 2)
  - 4. Cheri Daniels, Governor's Residence (Box Box 2)
    - Cover Title: Family First Cookbook: Recipes from Indiana's First Lady Cheri Daniels. Description: Inscription by the author, 2005. Indianapolis, Indiana, 2005. Printed by Sport Graphics, INC. Designed by Sara Weiskittel. 124 p.: ill.; 22 cm. Black wire spiral binding, with illustrated covers. (Box Box 2)
  - 5. Children's Bureau of Indianapolis, WTHR, Channel 13, and Kroger Food Stores (Box Box 2)
    - Cover Title: Kroger Food Stores and WTHR, Channel 13 present Celebrity Cookbook, Benefiting "Project Love" of the Indianapolis Children's Bureau. Title: Celebrity Cookbook. Description: Indianapolis, IN. 79 p.: ill.; 22 cm. Black comb binding, with illustrated covers. (Box Box 2)
  - 6. Christian Church (Box Box 2)
    - Cover Title: Winslow's Favorite Recipes Compiled by the U.R. Welcome Class of the Christian Church. Description: Winslow, Indiana, 1950. Burn marks on back pages. 50 p.: ill., index, beauty, household, diet, and kitchen tips; 23 cm. Black comb binding, with illustrated front cover. (Box Box 2)
  - 7. Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-Day Saints (Box Box 2)
    - Cover Title: Good Eating! Description: Bloomington, IN, 1983. Compiled by the Relief Society of the Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-Day Saints. 147 p.: index; 23 cm. Brownish red comb binding, with illustrated front cover. (Box Box 2)
  - 8. Columbus Senior Citizens (Box Box 2)
    - Cover Title: Columbus Senior Citizen's Cook Book. Title: A Book of Favorite Recipes Compiled by the Senior Center Club of Columbus, Indiana. Description: Columbus, Indiana, ~1987. "Our cover and divider sheets were designed by nationally known artist: W. Harold Hancock"-verso title. 96 p.: ill.; 23 cm. Black comb binding, with illustrated front cover. (Box Box 2)
  - 9. Community Hospital Auxiliary (Box Box 2)
    - Cover Title: Prescriptions for Good Eating. Description: La Porte, IN, 1962. 50 p.: ill., index; 23 cm. Brown comb binding, with illustrated covers. (Box Box 2)
  - 10. Daina Chamness (Box Box 2)
    - Cover Title: LifeSpice. Spine Title: LifeSpice. Title: LifeSpice: A book of recipes, remembrances, and hand-me-down wisdom. Description:Greenwood, Indiana, 1997. By Daina G. Chamness. Published by Ropkey Graphics, Global Digital Productions. 141 p.: index; 21 cm. In illustrated wrappers. (Box Box 2)
  - 11. Dames Club (Box Box 2)
    - Cover Title: Idea Cookbook. Description: Bloomington, Indiana. Includes recipes donated by Indiana University state, including Herman B. Wells. 205 p.: ill. by hand; 28 cm. Red comb binding, with hand illustrated front cover. (Box Box 2)
  - 12. Different Abilities (Box Box 2)
    - Cover Title: A Cookbook of Favorite Recipes by Celebrities and Friends of Different Abilities. Description: Bloomington, Indiana, 2006. Printed by Jumbo Jack's Cookbooks: Audubon, IA. 132 p.: ill., index, advertisements; 22 cm. Red plastic spiral binding, with illustrated covers. (Box Box 2)
  - 13. Durbin Hotel (Box Box 2)
    - Cover Title: Recipes of the Durbin. Title: Recipes of the Durbin: A Country Inn. Description: Rushville, Indiana, 1979. 155 p.: ill., index; 22 cm. Black comb binding. (Box Box 2)
  - 14. Elk's Ladies Organization, B.P.O.E. #446 (Box Box 2)
    - Cover Title: Treasured Recipes. Title: Ladies of Elks: The Organization with a Heart. Description: Bloomington, Indiana, 1987. Compiled by the Elk's Ladies Organization, B.P.O.E. #446. 70 p.: ill., index, blank notes; 23 cm. Blue comb binding, with illustrated front cover. (Box Box 2)
  - 15. English Wesleyan Church (Box Box 2)
    - Cover Title: Our Favorite Recipes. Title: A Book of Favorite Recipes. Description: English, IN, 1987. Compiled by the Women's Missionary Society of the English Wesleyan Church. Handwritten recipe, butterfinger dessert. 132 p.: ill., index; 22 cm. Tan comb binding, with illustrated front cover. (Box Box 2)
  - 16. English Wesleyan Church (Box Box 2)
    - Cover Title: Our Favorite Recipes, Volume II. Title: A Book of Favorite Recipes, Volume II. Description: English, IN, 1990. Compiled by the Women's Missionary Society of the English Wesleyan Church. 166 p.: ill., index; 22 cm. Black comb binding, with illustrated front cover. (Box Box 2)
  - 17. English Wesleyan Church (Box Box 2)
    - Cover Title: Our Favorite Recipes, Volume III. Title: A Book of Favorite Recipes, Volume III. Description: English, IN, 1999. Compiled by the Women's Missionary Society of the English Wesleyan Church. 192 p.: ill., index; 22 cm. Red comb binding, with illustrated front cover. (Box Box 2)
  - 18. Eva Emery Doty (Box Box 2)
    - Cover Title: Favorite Recipes from my Kitchen compiled by Eva Emery Doty, 2001. Description: Nashville, Indiana, 2001. Inscribed, "To June McGlasson for her cookbook collection from Eva Doty, Oct. 20, 2002. Includes newspaper cutout of Eva Doty's obituary, along with a photograph of Eva and photocopies of the cover. Edits to recipes in pencil. 44 p.: ill., index; 28 cm. Black comb binding, with clear plastic sheet over front cover, illustrated. (Box Box 2)
  - 19. Evening Belles Home Demonstration Club (Box Box 2)
    - Cover Title: Favorite Recipes: Evening Belles Home Demonstration Club in cooperation with Monroe County Home Demonstration Club. Description: Bloomington, Indiana, 1962. 102 p.: ill., index; 23 cm. Brown comb binding, with illustrated covers. (Box Box 2)
  - 20. First Baptist Church (American Baptist Cooks) (Box Box 2)
    - Cover Title: American Baptist Cooks...Their Favorite Recipes: First Baptists Church, La Porte, Indiana, 1982. Description: La Porte, Indiana, 1982. Inscribed "June from Alice, Feb. 1986." 193 p.: ill., index; 22 cm. White comb binding, with illustrated front cover. (Box Box 2)
  - 21. First Baptist Church (Chef's Cookery) (Box Box 2)
    - Cover Title: Chef's Cookery. Title: Presented by The Thomasine Allen Circle of the First Baptists Church. Description: La Porte, Indiana. Missing pages and back cover after "Salads." ~150 p.: ill.; 23 cm. Black comb binding at top, with illustrated front cover. (Box Box 2)
  - 22. First Christian Church, Disciples of Christ (Box Box 2)
    - Cover Title: Heavenly Delights. Description: Bloomington, IN, 1990. 193 p.: index; 23 cm. Black comb binding, with illustrated front cover. (Box Box 2)
  - 23. First United Methodist Church (Our Best to You) (Box Box 2)
    - Cover Title: Our Best to You. Description: La Porte, Indiana, 1979. Compiled by the Eve Group, United Methodist Women. Inscribed, "To June from Myrtle. A world of good wishes and fun in the kitchen. My recipes- 195, 233, 268, 241." 354 p.: ill.; 22 cm. Black comb binding, with illustrated front cover. (Box Box 2)
  - 24. First United Methodist Church (Favorite Recipes) (Box Box 2)
    - Cover Title: Favorite Recipes of First United Methodist Church Bloomington, Indiana 1981. Description: Bloomington, Indiana, 1981. 23 p.: 22 cm. Black comb binding, with illustrated front cover. (Box Box 2)
  - 25. First United Methodist Church (Parent's Day Out) (Box Box 2)
    - Cover Title: Cookbook: Parent's Day Out. Description: Bloomington, IN, 1991. 71 p.: ill., index; 23 cm. White comb binding, with illustrated front cover. (Box Box 2)
  - 1. The Franklin United Methodist Home (Box Box 3)
    - Cover Title: Our Favorite Recipes. Description: Franklin, Indiana. Compiled by Residents, Cottagers, and Employees of Franklin United Methodist Home. 122 p.: ill., index; 23 cm. Tan comb binding, with illustrated front cover. (Box Box 3)
  - 2. Handy-cap Horizons, Inc. (Box Box 3)
    - Cover Title: Favorite Dishes of Famous People. Title: Favorite Dishes of Famous People. Description: Indianapolis, IN: 1965. Edited by Dorothy S. Axsom, with artwork by Ruth Coates. 140 p.,: ill., index; 22 cm. White comb binding, with illustrated front cover. (Box Box 3)
  - 3. Indiana Colonial Dames of the Seventeenth Century (Box Box 3)
    - Cover Title: Cooking Like a Dame: Receipts of the Indiana Colonial Dames of the Seventeenth Century. Title: Cooking Like a Dame: Receipts of the Indiana Colonial Dames of the Seventeenth Century. Description: Statewide, 2004. 108 p.: ill.; 22 cm. Black spiral binding, with illustrated front cover. (Box Box 3)
  - 4. Indiana Daughters of the American Revolution (Box Box 3)
    - Cover Title: Indiana DAR Cookbook. Spine Title: Indiana DAR Cookbook. Title: Indiana DAR Cookbook. Description: 1980. 253 p.: ill., index; 24 cm. Metal ring binding, with plastic binder and section tabs. (Box Box 3)
  - 5. Indiana State Fair (Box Box 3)
    - Cover Title: Indiana State Fair Cookbook, First Edition. Spine Title: Indiana State Fair Cookbook, First Edition. Title: Indiana State Fair Cookbook, First Edition. Description: Indianapolis, Indiana, 1989. State Fair Books. Edited by Judi K. Merkel. 159 p.: index; 23 cm. Bound in wire spiral, with illustrated covers. (Box Box 3)
  - 6. Indiana State Museum (Box Box 3)
    - Cover Title: Indiana State Museum presents L.S. Ayres Tea Room: Recipes and Recollections. Title: L.S. Ayres Tea Room: Recipes and Recollections compiled by Indiana State Museum. Second Title: L.S. Ayres Tea Room: Recipes and Recollections made possible through the generosity of the Ayres Foundation, Inc. with assistance provided by the Indiana State Museum Foundation and with very special thanks extended to Nancy Fernandes. Description: Indianapolis, Indiana, 1998. Indianapolis: Indiana State Museum. 69 p.: ill. and photography by Indiana Historical Society and Harold Lee Miller, index, blank notes section; 23 cm. Black spiral binding, with illustrated front cover. (Box Box 3)
  - 7. Indianapolis Sesquicentennial Commission (Box Box 3)
    - Cover Title: Sesqui-Samplings: 150 Years of Cooking in Indianapolis. Spine Title: 1821-1971, Sesqui-Samplings. Title: Sesqui-Saplings: 150 Years of Cooking in Indianapolis. Description: Indianapolis, Indiana, 1971. By the Indianapolis Sesquicentennial Commission. Inscribed, "To Aunt June on her birthday, 1971. From Debbie" and "Darla Wolfe." 114 p.: ill., index; 27 cm. Tan comb binding, with illustrated boards. (Box Box 3)
  - 8. Iota Chapter of Kappa Kappa Sigma (Box Box 3)
    - Cover Title: Iota Chapter, Kappa Kappa Sigma, 1927-2009: Celebrating 82 years. Title: A Kappa Kappa Sigma Cookbook as it should be...assembled for your cooking pleasure by Iota Chapter. Description: Bloomington, Indiana. Lenexa: Cookbook Publishers, Inc., 2009. 136 p.: ill., index; 22 cm. Blue comb binding, illustrated front cover. (Box Box 3)
  - 9. The IU Cookbook (Box Box 3)
    - Cover Title: The IU Cookbook. Spine Title: The IU Cookbook. Title: The IU Cookbook. Description: Indianapolis, Indiana, 1993. By Terry Murray. 180 p.: ill., index; 24 cm. Bound in red boards, with dj. (Box Box 3)
  - 10. James Whitcomb Riley (Box Box 3)
    - Cover Title: The James Whitcomb Riley Cookbook. Title:The James Whitcomb Riley Cookbook. Description: Indianapolis, IN, 1990. By Dorothy June Williams and Diana Williams Hansen. 213 p.: ill.; 23 cm. (Box Box 3)
  - 11. Junior Achievement, Senior Economics (Box Box 3)
    - Cover Title: Senior Economics Presents...The Celebrity Cookbook. Description: Shelbyville, Indiana, 1987-1988. Bear Batch, Junior Achievement: An Applied Economics Company. ~100 p.: ill; 23 cm. Black comb binding, with clear covers. (Box Box 3)
  - 12. Kappa Kappa Kappa (Celebrate the Seasons) (Box Box 3)
    - Cover Title: Celebrate the Seasons: Kappa Kappa Kappa, Washington, Indiana. Spine Title: Celebrate the Seasons. Title: Celebrate the Seasons. Description: Washington, Indiana, 1991. 300 p.: ill., index; 23 cm. White comb binding, with illustrated front cover. (Box Box 3)
  - 13. Kappa Kappa Kappa (tri kappa cooks!) (Box Box 3)
    - Cover Title: tri kappa cooks! Title: Alpha Chapter of Kappa Kappa Kappa, Bloomington, Indiana, 1982: tri kappa cooks! Description: Bloomington, IN 1982. 222 p.: colored section dividers, blank notes section, index; 25 cm. White comb binding, with illustrated covers. (Box Box 3)
  - 14. Kiwanis International (Box Box 3)
    - Cover Title: Kiwanis International, Indiana District: Our Best Cooks Show and Tell. Description: Indiana, 1989. "Published and Printed by Cookbook Publishers, Inc...Olathe, Kansas"--Verso table of contents. 271 p.: ill., blank notes, index, kitchen tips (i, viii); 23 cm. Cream comb binding, with illustrated front cover. (Box Box 3)
  - 15. La Porte County Library (Box Box 3)
    - Cover Title: Favorite Recipes from La Porte County Kitchens. Description: La Porte County Library, 1968. 36 p.: 22 cm. In illustrated wrappers. (Box Box 3)
  - 16. La Porte Hospital Auxiliary (Heavenly Salads and Casseroles) (Box Box 3)
    - Cover Title: Heavenly Salads and Casseroles, Presented by La Porte Hospital Auxiliary. Description: La Porte, Indiana. Recipes from newspaper included. 127 p.: index, ill.; 22 cm. Black comb binding, with illustrated front cover. (Box Box 3)
  - 17. La Porte Hospital Auxiliary (Heavenly Desserts) (Box Box 3)
    - Cover Title: Heavenly Desserts, Inspired by La Porte Hospital Auxiliary. Description: La Porte, Indiana. 99 p.: index, ill.; 22 cm. Black comb binding, with illustrated front cover. (Box Box 3)
  - 18. Ladies Fellowship of Sherwood Oaks Christian Church (Box Box 3)
    - Cover Title: Cooking with Love. Title: Recipes compiled by Ladies Oaks Christian Church. Description: Bloomington, IN. Waseca: Walter's Cookbooks. 148 p.: ill., index; 23 cm. Red comb binding, with illustrated front cover. (Box Box 3)
  - 19. Lazarus Restaurants (Box Box 3)
    - Cover Title: Recipes from Our Kitchen. Lazarus: Celebrating 100 years of fine food. Description: Various recipes from Lazarus Restaurants scattered across Indiana. 96 p.: ill.; 24 cm. Green comb binding, with illustrated covers. (Box Box 3)
  - 20. Lazarus Restaurants (Box Box 3)
    - Cover Title: Recipes II from Our Kitchen. Lazarus: Celebrating 100 years of fine food. Description: Various recipes from Lazarus Restaurants scattered across Indiana. 120 p.: ill.; 24 cm. Clear comb binding, with illustrated covers. (Box Box 3)
  - 1. Lin Davis (Box Box 4)